A Guide to the Impressed Property Claim Records of the Auditor of Public Accounts, 1776-1794
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Impressed Property Claim Records of the Auditor of Public Accounts, 1776-1797
The Library of Virginia
APA 237, APA 238, APA 239, APA 240, APA 241, APA 242, APA 243, APA 244
XX cu. ft. (XX boxes)
LVA
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
These materials are available on microfilm and microfilm should be served instead of the originals:
Certficates, 1780-1783 (APA 241) available on microfilm, Revolutionary War Public Service Claims, Reels 8-18
Commissioner's Books, 1783 (APA 243) available on microfilm, Revolutionary War Public Service Claims, Reels 1-6
Court Booklets: Indexes and Lists, 1781-1783 (APA 242) available on microfilm, Revolutionary War Public Service Claims, Reels 1-4
Acquisition Information
Transferred by the Auditor of Public Accounts in 1913.
Historical Information
During the Revolution the Virginia General Assmebly authorized the procurement of supplies from its citizens for the use of the militia, state, and Continental troops. The Legislature, sitting in sessions between 1780 May 4 and 1780 July 14, passed "An act for procuring a supply of provisions and other necessaries for the use of the Army" [Hening 10:233-237]. This act, extended in other sessions, authorized the governor to appoint commissioners within each county to impress such supplies and services as were thought necessary to the war effort.
The commissioners issued receipts, or certificates, to individuals for the requisitioned items so that owners could seek reimbursement from the state government. The certificates and any other available documentation was presented to the county court during special sessions held between 1781 and 1783. Certificates were examined and authenticated by the courts, and the amount of compensation was determined. Information pertaining to claims that were approved was recorded by the court clerk in court booklets which were sent to the public service claims commissioners' office in Richmond. The local provision law commissioners and deputy commissaries also kept lists of foodstuffs, animals and other provisions that were collected in each county.
Two public service claims commissioners were appointed by the governor in 1783 to authorize reimbursement for materials and services provided. Individuals or their agents went to the commissioner's office in Richmond where payment on their claims was approved based on information contained in the certificates and court booklets. These transactions were recorded in the commissioners' books. The individual or his agent was then issued a warrant by the Auditor of Public Accounts which he in turn took to the state treasurer's office for payment.
Scope and Content
Impressed Property Claims Records, 1776-1797, including certificates, claims, commissioner's booklets, court booklets, indexes, lists, orders, property valuations, registers and vouchers, related to compensation from the state made by Virginia citizens for materials, supplies, and personal services provided to militia, State and Continental troops during the Revolutionary War.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically into eight series. This collection consists of several Auditor of Public Accounts (APA) accessions that while identified separately, all pertain to the same collection of records. Since the specific APA accessions had been used and referenced over the years it was decided that while each distinct APA accession number would be maintained separately, one finding aid could describe the entire collection. Each series references it's specific APA accession number.
Series I: Certificates, 1780-1783 (APA 241)
Series II: Claims reaudited - Orders and vouchers, 1779-1786 (APA 239)
Series III: Commissioner's books, 1783 (APA 243)
Series IV: Computations and memoranda on property valuations, 1776-1783, 1786, 1791 (APA 237)
Series V: Court booklets, indexes and lists, 1781-1783 (APA 242)
Series VI: General claims approved, 1777, 1779-1784, 1789-1790, 1794 (APA 238)
Series VII: Rejected claims lists, 1780, 1784-1785, n.d. (APA 240)
Series VIII: Warrant register, 1783 July 10-August 24 (APA 244)
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1988-1994, 2006.
  - 1984-1992 (bulk 1991) (Accession 36853)., 58 cu. ft. (58 boxes)
    This accession is arranged in no discernable order, though there are some alphabetical sequences.
    - Accidents involving state owned vehicles, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Africanized honey bee, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - AG Diversification Conference (Lynchburg), 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agreements, 1989-1991. (Box 1)
    - Agribusiness Council, Virginia, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agribusiness Parks, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agriculture, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agriculture in the classroom, 1989-1991. (Box 1)
    - Agricultural Hall of Fame, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Agricultural Opportunities Commission, 1980. (Box 1)
    - Air Pollution Control, Dept. of, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - Aldicarb, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - American Agricultural Movement of Virginia, 1984-1991. (Box 1)
    - American Dairy Association, 1988-1991. (Box 1)
    - American Dairy Association of Virginia, 1991. (Box 1)
    - American Sheep Federation, 1990. (Box 1)
    - Angola, 1987-1991. (Box 1)
    - Animal Damage Control Program, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Appropriation Committee - House of Delegates, 1984-1990. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Executive Committee, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Junior Scholarship Program, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Premiums Committee, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition - Program briefing, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Bees, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Biotechnology Task Force, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - Carroll County Farmers Market, 1989. (Box 1)
    - Center for Rural Development, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Central Farmers Market, 1989. (Box 1)
    - Certified Seed Board, State - Meeting, 1991 Dec. (Box 1)
    - Chesapeake Bay (general information), 1991. (Box 1)
    - Chincoteague, Town of, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Civil Rights, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Clean Air Act, 1989-1991. (Box 1)
    - Clean Water Act, 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - Cockfighting, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Code Commission, Virginia, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Colonial Farm Credit (Earl Longest), 1990-1991. (Box 1)
    - Council on the Environment - Scoping Oil/Gas, 1991. (Box 1)
    - Administration and Planning, Division of, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Combined Charitable Campaign, 1990-1991. (Box 2)
    - Commission on Population Growth, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Communication, Office of, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Comptroller, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1989-1991. (Box 2)
    - Conservation Leadership Project, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services, Division of, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Consolidated Laboratory Services Advisory Board - Meeting, 1991 Sept. (Box 2)
    - Cotton Gin (general information), 1991. (Box 2)
    - Council of Information Management, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Council on the Environment, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Council on State Governments, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Council on the Environment - Meeting, 1991 June. (Box 2)
    - Coyote control, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Dairy Tour (Harrisonburg), 1991 Sept. (Box 2)
    - Deer farming, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Delmarva Poultry Industry, Inc., 1989-1991. (Box 2)
    - Delmarva Chicken Festival, 1991 June. (Box 2)
    - Desert Storm, 1991. (Box 2)
    - New Uses Council, 1991. (Box 2)
    - Assistant Attorney General, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Consumer Affairs, Division of, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Dairy and Foods, Division of, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Facilities Coordinator, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Finance Office, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Fiscal Manager, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Herb Hill - Strategic planning, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Human Resources - Assistant Director, 1989-1991. (Box 3)
    - Human Resources - Director, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Information Systems, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Internal Auditor, 1991. (Box 3)
    - )Longworth meeting, 1991 May. (Box 3)
    - Purchasing Director, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Virginia Solicitation of Contributions, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Animal Health, Division of, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Animal Care position paper, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Animal Health, Southwest Virginia Advisory Committee on, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Animal Wardens, 1988. (Box 3)
    - Animal Welfare issues, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Avian Influenza Outbreak, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Duck/Bird kill in Southeast Virginia, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Egg Quality Assurance Council, 1990. (Box 3)
    - Equine Infectious Anemia Advisory Committee, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Humane treatment at horse auctions, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Managing Avian Influenza and other poultry diseases, 1990-1991. (Box 3)
    - Meat and Poultry Inspection, 1991. (Box 3)
    - Mid-Atlantic Poultry Health Council, 1991 June. (Box 3)
    - Pseudorabies Virus Committee, 1987-1991. (Box 3)
    - National Consumers Week, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Marketing Division, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Finvest Foods, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Forest Products Specialist, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - International Marketing, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Wine Marketing Specialish, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - Meeting with Robert Gomperts, 1991. (Box 4)
    - International Marketing staff meeting, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Southwest Virginia Farmers Market Board, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - Legislative Trail Ride, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Direct Leave Share Pilot Program, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Drought, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Drought in California, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Weekly reports to Secretary Framme, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Agency Head meeting, 1991 Mar. (Box 4)
    - Equine Marketing of Virginia, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - Agency Head meeting, 1991 June. (Box 4)
    - Agency Head meeting, 1991 July. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Plan, Virginia, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Farmers Market Study, 1985. (Box 4)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1988-1991. (Box 4)
    - Farm bill, 1991. (Box 4)
    - Endangered Plants/Species/Insects, 1991. (Box 4)
    - EEO Advisory Committee, 1991-1992. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Impact Statements, 1990-1991. (Box 4)
    - Economic Recovery - Virginia, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Economic Recovery Commission, Virginia (HJR 433), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Earth Day 1990, 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - Economic Development, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Film Office, Virginia, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Forestry, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Forestry Task Force, Southside (House Document 42), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Forestry School Study, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Commissioner's Agriculture Forum, 1991 May. (Box 5)
    - Food and Libations Association of Virginia (FLAVA), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Furadan (general information), 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - Foreign Agricultural Investment, 1984-1991. (Box 5)
    - Future Farmers of American, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Federal legislators, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Farm Credit Council, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Federal legislation, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Food Watch, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Federal-State Marketing Improvement, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Friends of Industry and Agriculture (FIA), 1983-1991. (Box 5)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 5)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Governor's European Trade Mission, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Governor's Pacific Rim Mission, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Governor's Open House, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Governor's Report of Rural Development, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Ginseng, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Groundwater, 1991. (Box 5)
    - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT), 1989-1991. (Box 5)
    - Granville P. Mead (Trust), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Hemp, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Holiday Blanket Campaign, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Hotel information, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Horse Breeder Incentive Program, 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - Horses (general information), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Horticulture Society, Virginia State, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Incentive Pay Plan, 1990-1991. (Box 5)
    - JLARC, 1991. (Box 5)
    - IUG Charter, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Information Technoloty, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Kuwait, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Lab Services Management Study, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Lamb Cooperative, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Livestock Export Facility (Blackstone), 1991. (Box 5)
    - Farm Winery Law, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Hong Kong/Tokyo Office information, 1989-1990. (Box 5)
    - News clippings, 1991. (Box 5)
    - Policy Analysis and Development, Division of, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Food Distribution Section, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Pesticide Managemtn, Office of, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Product and Industry Regulation, Division of, 1991. (Box 6)
    - PAIR Assistant Director, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Potato hearing, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Gypsy Moth (general information), 1991. (Box 6)
    - Weights and Measure (Virginia Beach), 1990-1991. (Box 6)
    - Boll Weevil Eradication Program, 1988-1991. (Box 6)
    - Weights and Measures Association meeting, 1991 Aug. (Box 6)
    - Seed Laboratory Services, 1985-1991. (Box 6)
    - SFIREG, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Pesticide appeal, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Agricultural Statistics Service, 1990-1991. (Box 6)
    - VDACS/State Boards and Commissions, 1991. (Box 6)
    - Virginia Crops and Livestock (newsletter), 1989-1991. (Box 6)
    - Proposed 1990-1991 Budget Addenda, 1990-1991. (Box 7)
    - EEO/Affirmative Action, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Press Report on Animal Health and Seed Testing Lab, 1990-1991. (Box 7)
    - VDACS Information Users Group, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Abingdon/Roanoke Office, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Biennium Budget 1992-1994 (information), 1991. (Box 7)
    - Furlough Task Force, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Budget Reduction 6% (1991-1992), 1991. (Box 7)
    - Task Group on Information Function, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Budget - Revised Appropriation Act, 1991. (Box 7)
    - VDACS Marketing Accomplishments, 1990-1991. (Box 7)
    - James City Farmers Market, 1991. (Box 7)
    - VDACS Temporary Workforce Reduction Plan, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Early Retirement issues and concerns, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Legislative Proposals, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Blankenship, Donald G. - Deputy Commissioner, 1992. (Box 7)
    - Organization and Management Study, 1991. (Box 7)
    - Marketing Exchange Group (MEG), 1991. (Box 7)
    - Marketing Exchange Group (MEG) - meeting, 1991 Apr. (Box 7)
    - Marketing Exchange Group (MEG) - meeting, 1991 Aug. (Box 7)
    - Migrant/Seasonal Farm Workers Board, 1989-1991. (Box 7)
    - Market Basket Food Price Surveys, 1982-1991. (Box 7)
    - Migrant Worker Policy Committee, Interagency, 1990. (Box 7)
    - Nottoway Teaching/Demonstration Farm, 1989-1991. (Box 7)
    - National Governors Association, 1991. (Box 7)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - grant, 1991-1992. (Box 7)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Mexico Agricultural Accord, 1990. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Mid-Year Conference, 1991 Mar. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Washington Office reports, 1991. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - general information, 1991. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - NASDA/USDA Task Force, 1991 Aug. (Box 8)
    - National Association of State Departments of Agriculture (NASDA) - Food and Agriculture Exposition, 1991. (Box 8)
    - National Agriculture Week, 1991 Mar. (Box 8)
    - National 4H Engineering, 1991. (Box 8)
    - State-Provinces Agriculture Accord, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Nursery Industry Study/Survey, 1991. (Box 8)
    - National Association of Conservation Districts - newsletter, 1988-1991. (Box 8)
    - Organic Standards Advisory Board, National, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Organic (general information), 1991. (Box 8)
    - President's Enterprise Initiative, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Private Property Rights Act of 1991, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Pennfield, 1991. (Box 8)
    - People to People Citizen Ambassador, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Personnel and Training, Dep.t of, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Planning/Development, 1987. (Box 8)
    - Peanuts (general information), 1991. (Box 8)
    - Purcell, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Potatoes - States/Canada, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Prompt reports, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Radiation Advisory Board, 1991. (Box 8)
    - REAP - Blackstone, 1991 July. (Box 8)
    - Rail Industry Access, 1990. (Box 8)
    - Register of Regulations, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Records Management, 1990-1991. (Box 8)
    - Referendum - Virginia Small Grain Producers, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Referendum - Sweet Potato, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Regional meetings, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Recycling Collection Program, 1989-1991. (Box 8)
    - Retail Food Special Advisory Comm, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Rural Virginia Development, 1991. (Box 8)
    - Rural Economic Analysis Program, 1991. (Box 8)
    - ROCCO Open House, 1991 Sept. (Box 8)
    - Rural Development Committee, 1991. (Box 8)
  - 1994, 2004 (Accession 43628)., 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes)
    This accession is arranged in no discernable order.
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 1994. (Box 1)
    - Weekly Reports to the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994. (Box 1)
    - Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994. (Box 1)
    - Commissioner's general correspondence - J. Carlton Courter, III, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Blankenship, Donald, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Commissioner's Office - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Memos - SMT, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Dickenson, William P., 1994. (Box 2)
    - Adams, Sandra, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Administrative and Financial Services, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Development Services, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Farmland Preservation, Office of, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Jackson, Karen E., 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - HRO, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Internal Auditor, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Seward, Roy E., 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Policy Planning and Research, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Giles, Perida, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Agriculture Stewardship, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Lidholm, Elaine, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Communications and Promotion, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Alvarez, Andy - Consumer Affairs, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Consumer Affairs - Annual Report, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Fulgham, Frank - Office of Plant and Pest Services, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Endangered Species, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Lawson, Marvin - Consumer Protection, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Consumer Protection, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous - Animal and Food Industry Services, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Pesticides, 1994. (Box 2)
    - Correspondence/Financials (M. Craig Halbleib and Donald Blankenship), 1994. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Information Systems, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Garey, Louis, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Martin, Teddy, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Procurement, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Cardin, David, Dr., 1994. (Box 3)
    - Bulls, Donald, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Pesticides, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Metolachlor, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Rogers, Alan - Office of Product and Industry Standards, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Weights and Measures - Legisltive proposals, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Weights and Measures - Impact of Reduction, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Dairy and Food, Office of, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Food Security - Dairy, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Sleight, Thomas, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Division of Marketing, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Accounts, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Agendas - SMT, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Agricultural Spraying - Best Practices, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Amendments - General Assembly, 1994. (Box 3)
    - ABC Board, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Amendments - Governor, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Apple Board, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Atlantic Rural Exposition, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Attorney General, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Avian Influenza, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Awards and Recognition - VDACS, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Awards Committee - VDACS, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Black Farmers Association, National, 1994. (Box 3)
    - BSE, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Cattle Grading fees, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Chippokes Plantation Farm Foundation, 1994. (Box 3)
    - CVC, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Commodity Boards, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Commission on Local Government, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Continuity of Operations Plan, 1994. (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous - Finance Office, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Council of State Governments, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Coyotes, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Dairy Compact, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Dairymen's Association of Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Delegates, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Delmarva Poultry, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Disposal Agreement AI, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Disasters, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 1994. (Box 4)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Equine Industry Study, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Farmland and Forest Land Preservation - Annual Report, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Education, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Emerald Ash Borer, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Farmer's Market System Report, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Food Policy Council, 1994. (Box 4)
    - FOIA, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Governor's Office, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Health Dept., 1994. (Box 4)
    - Homeland Security, 1994. (Box 4)
    - House Council - Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - H. J. Resolution No. 228, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Human Resources Management, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Information Technology Agency, Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Interior, U. S. Dept. of the, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Information Management, Council on, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Invasive Species Work Group, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Hot Case, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Housing and Community Development, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Land Use, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Library of Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Legislative guidelines, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Legislative Services, Div. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Legislation, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Milk, Raw - Sale of - Cow Sharing, 1994. (Box 4)
    - MOU to Control Tropical Soda Apple, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Milk Commission, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Natural Resources, Secretary of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Perdue, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Pilgrims Pride, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Pork Industry Association, Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Poultry Growers Cooperative, Virginia, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Procurement Management - Review Report, 1994. (Box 4)
    - S. J. Resolution No. 57, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Senators, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Soil and Water Conservation, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Sole Source, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Solem, Christine, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Security Position - Agricultural, 1994. (Box 4)
    - VDACS Reports to the General Assembly, 1994. (Box 4)
    - Eastern Shore Agriculture Conference and Trade Show, 1994 Jan 6-7. (Box 5)
    - Colonial Soil and Water Conservation District, 2004. (Box 5)
    - VITA - Medium and Large Agency Transition Workshop, 2004. (Box 5)